<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Catalogue</string>
    <string name="judul_film">Judul</string>
    <string name="release">Rilis</string>
    <string name="ringkasan">Ringkasan</string>
    <string name="durasi">Durasi</string>
    <string name="read_more">Lanjutkan Membaca</string>

    <string-array name="data_title">
        <item>Guardian of the Galaxy</item>
        <item>Ant Man</item>
        <item>Doctor Strange</item>
        <item>Spider-Man: Homecoming</item>
        <item>Thor: Ragnarok</item>
        <item>Black Panther</item>
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Ant-Man and The Wasp</item>
        <item>Captain Marvel</item>
        <item>Avengers: Endgame</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="release_date">
        <item>2014</item>
        <item>2015</item>
        <item>2016</item>
        <item>2017</item>
        <item>2017</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="duration">
        <item>2h 5m</item>
        <item>1h 58m</item>
        <item>1h 55m</item>
        <item>2h 13m</item>
        <item>2h 10m</item>
        <item>2h 15m</item>
        <item>2h 40m</item>
        <item>2h 5m</item>
        <item>2h 5m</item>
        <item>3h 2m</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="pic">
        <item>@drawable/guardian</item>
        <item>@drawable/ant</item>
        <item>@drawable/doctor</item>
        <item>@drawable/spider</item>
        <item>@drawable/thor</item>
        <item>@drawable/panther</item>
        <item>@drawable/infinitywar</item>
        <item>@drawable/ant2</item>
        <item>@drawable/captain</item>
        <item>@drawable/endgame</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="overview">
        <item>Light years from Earth, 26 years after being abducted, Peter Quill finds himself the prime target of a manhunt after discovering an orb wanted by Ronan the Accuser.</item>
        <item>Armed with the astonishing ability to shrink in scale but increase in strength, master thief Scott Lang must embrace his inner-hero and help his mentor, Doctor Hank Pym, protect the secret behind his spectacular Ant-Man suit from a new generation of towering threats. Against seemingly insurmountable obstacles, Pym and Lang must plan and pull off a heist that will save the world.</item>
        <item>After his career is destroyed, a brilliant but arrogant surgeon gets a new lease on life when a sorcerer takes him under her wing and trains him to defend the world against evil.</item>
        <item>Following the events of Captain America: Civil War, Peter Parker, with the help of his mentor Tony Stark, tries to balance his life as an ordinary high school student in Queens, New York City, with fighting crime as his superhero alter ego Spider-Man as a new threat, the Vulture, emerges.</item>
        <item>Thor is imprisoned on the other side of the universe and finds himself in a race against time to get back to Asgard to stop Ragnarok, the destruction of his home-world and the end of Asgardian civilization, at the hands of an all-powerful new threat, the ruthless Hela.</item>
        <item>King T\'Challa returns home from America to the reclusive, technologically advanced African nation of Wakanda to serve as his country\'s new leader. However, T Challa soon finds that he is challenged for the throne by factions within his own country as well as without. Using powers reserved to Wakandan kings, T\'Challa assumes the Black Panther mantel to join with girlfriend Nakia, the queen-mother, his princess-kid sister, members of the Dora Milaje (the Wakandan special forces) and an American secret agent, to prevent Wakanda from being dragged into a world war.</item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</item>
        <item>Just when his time under house arrest is about to end, Scott Lang once again puts his freedom at risk to help Hope van Dyne and Dr. Hank Pym dive into the quantum realm and try to accomplish, against time and any chance of success, a very dangerous rescue mission.</item>
        <item>The story follows Carol Danvers as she becomes one of the universe’s most powerful heroes when Earth is caught in the middle of a galactic war between two alien races. Set in the 1990s, Captain Marvel is an all-new adventure from a previously unseen period in the history of the Marvel Cinematic Universe.</item>
        <item>After the devastating events of Avengers: Infinity War, the universe is in ruins due to the efforts of the Mad Titan, Thanos. With the help of remaining allies, the Avengers must assemble once more in order to undo Thanos\' actions and restore order to the universe once and for all, no matter what consequences may be in store.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="titleTvShow">
        <item>Chernobyl</item>
        <item>Sherlock</item>
        <item>Hunter x Hunter</item>
        <item>Avatar The Last Airbender</item>
        <item>Planet Earth II</item>
        <item>Band Of Brothers</item>
        <item>Stranger Things</item>
        <item>Black Mirror</item>
        <item>The Haunting of Hill House</item>
        <item>Human Planet</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="rilisShow">
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2010</item>
        <item>2011</item>
        <item>2005</item>
        <item>2016</item>
        <item>2001</item>
        <item>2016</item>
        <item>2011</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2011</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="durasiShow">
        <item>70m</item>
        <item>90m</item>
        <item>24m</item>
        <item>25m</item>
        <item>60m</item>
        <item>60m</item>
        <item>50m</item>
        <item>55m</item>
        <item>50m</item>
        <item>60m</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="picShow">
        <item>@drawable/chernobyl</item>
        <item>@drawable/sherlock</item>
        <item>@drawable/hunter</item>
        <item>@drawable/avatar</item>
        <item>@drawable/planet</item>
        <item>@drawable/band</item>
        <item>@drawable/stranger</item>
        <item>@drawable/black</item>
        <item>@drawable/haunting</item>
        <item>@drawable/humanplanet</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="ovShow">
        <item>A dramatization of the true story of one of the worst man-made catastrophes in history, the catastrophic nuclear accident at Chernobyl. A tale of the brave men and women who sacrificed to save Europe from unimaginable disaster.</item>
        <item>A modern update finds the famous sleuth and his doctor partner solving crime in 21st century London.</item>
        <item>Twelve-year-old Gon Freecss one day discovers that the father he had always been told was dead was alive and well. His Father, Ging, is a Hunter—a member of society\'s elite with a license to go anywhere or do almost anything. Gon, determined to follow in his father\'s footsteps, decides to take the Hunter Examination and eventually find his father to prove himself as a Hunter in his own right. But on the way, he learns that there is more to becoming a Hunter than previously thought, and the challenges that he must face are considered the toughest in the world.</item>
        <item>In a war-torn world of elemental magic, a young boy reawakens to undertake a dangerous mystic quest to fulfill his destiny as the Avatar, and bring peace to the world.</item>
        <item>David Attenborough presents a documentary series exploring how animals meet the challenges of surviving in the most iconic habitats on earth.</item>
        <item>Drawn from interviews with survivors of Easy Company, as well as their journals and letters, Band of Brothers chronicles the experiences of these men from paratrooper training in Georgia through the end of the war. As an elite rifle company parachuting into Normandy early on D-Day morning, participants in the Battle of the Bulge, and witness to the horrors of war, the men of Easy knew extraordinary bravery and extraordinary fear - and became the stuff of legend. Based on Stephen E. Ambrose\'s acclaimed book of the same name.</item>
        <item>When a young boy vanishes, a small town uncovers a mystery involving secret experiments, terrifying supernatural forces, and one strange little girl.</item>
        <item>A contemporary British re-working of The Twilight Zone with stories that tap into the collective unease about our modern world. Over the last ten years, technology has transformed almost every aspect of our lives before we\'ve had time to stop and question it. In every home; on every desk; in every palm - a plasma screen; a monitor; a smartphone - a black mirror of our 21st Century existence.</item>
        <item>The Crains, a fractured family, confront haunting memories of their old home and the terrifying events that drove them from it.</item>
        <item>A cinematic experience bringing you the most amazing human stories in the world. Humans and wildlife surviving in the most extreme environments on Earth.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="movies">FILM</string>
    <string name="tv_show">SERIAL TV</string>
    <string name="language">Pengaturan Bahasa</string>
</resources>
